<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<book	xmlns="http://docbook.org/ns/docbook"
		xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"
		version="5.0" xml:id="V120">
  <info>
	<title>V120 Linux Programmer's Manual</title>
	<authorgroup>
		<author>
			<personname><firstname>Rob</firstname><surname>Gaddi</surname></personname>
			<affiliation>
				<orgname>Highland Technology, Inc.</orgname>
				<address><email>rgaddi@highlandtechnology.com</email></address>
			</affiliation>
			<contrib>Author of v120irqd</contrib>
		</author>
	</authorgroup>

	<copyright>
		<year>2015</year>
		<holder>Highland Technology, Inc.</holder>
	</copyright>

	<legalnotice>
		<para>All rights reserved.</para>

		<para>Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without
		modification, are permitted provided that the following conditions are
		met:</para>

			<orderedlist inheritnum="ignore" continuation="restarts">
				<listitem><para>
	Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright notice, this
	list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
				</para></listitem><listitem><para>
	Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright notice,
	this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the documentation
	and/or other materials provided with the distribution.
				</para></listitem><listitem><para>
	Neither the name of the copyright holder nor the names of its contributors
	may be used to endorse or promote products derived from this software
	without specific prior written permission.
				</para></listitem>
			</orderedlist>

	<para>THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND
	CONTRIBUTORS "AS IS" AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING,
	BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND
	FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
	COPYRIGHT HOLDER OR CONTRIBUTORS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT,
	INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT
	NOT LIMITED TO, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF
	USE, DATA, OR PROFITS; OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON
	ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY, WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT
	(INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF
	THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.</para>
		</legalnotice>
	</info>
	<toc/>

	<chapter xml:id="intro"><info><title>Introduction</title></info>

		<para>
	The Linux interfaces to the V120 allow both the V120 itself and VME modules
	controlled by it to be accessed by userspace code, with no need to write
	kernel drivers other than the one provided for the V120.
		</para>
	</chapter>

	<xi:include href="v120_irq/v120irqd.xml" xpointer="_interrupts" />
	<xi:include href="v120_irq/v120irqd-api.xml" />
</book>
